# Francisco Veracoechea

Web Developer

## Profile

Passionate software developer and collaborative team player who specializes in web applications technologies, with a problem solving and creative mindset.

During my career, I have accumulated 3+ years of experience building scalable web applications using React.js, Node.js, Typescript, and Laravel. Currently in search of a position where I can continuously grow my development skills.

# Employment History

Full Stack Developer at Web Studios West, Remote (U.S.)

May 2020 — Present

- Designing custom website applications using React.js or Next.js in addition to Headless CMS for client data management
- Developing and designing full-stack e-Commerce applications
- Building custom mobile applications using React Native
- Developing back-end applications using Node.js
- Used: Knowledge of RESTful and Graphql APIs, Headless storefront, and PWA

# Web Developer at Oxoft.io, Lecheria, Vnz.

January 2018 — November 2019

- Developed custom web applications and APIs
- Built backend applications using Laravel
- Used technologies such as Laravel, Node.js, and React.js, and Typescript.

## Education

English as a Second Language, Interactive College Of Technology, Chamblee, GA

February 2019 — April 2020

Associate's degree Information Technology, IUTIRLA, Lecheria - Venezuela

2014 - 2017

Professional training to perform effectively and efficiently in the specific areas of analysis, design, implementation, and management information systems, as well as in computer project management.

#### **Details**

(281) 704-0847 f.v.borgia@gmail.com

#### Links

fveracoechea.com linkedin.com/in/fveracoechea github.com/fveracoechea

#### **Skills**

Frontend and Backend Development

**Browser Fundamentals** 

Responsive Design

Mobile Development

Accessible Interfaces

**Data Structures** 

#### Languages

**English** 

Spanish

## **Hobbies**

I enjoy spending my free time playing drums/guitar, doing physical activities, and learning about the latest technologies.